Gabriele Medeot

I am a Machine Learning Researcher and Software Engineer specialising in deep learning and generative models. I am able to build machine learning models extremely rapidly, and move them swiftly from prototype to production. I'm a fast learner and acquire new knowledge easily. I am also a musician, playing wind instruments: clarinet, saxophone and flute.

(+44) 07762246782 ghaelen.m@gmail.com

SELECTED WORKING EXPERIENCE

Bytedance, London (UK) — Senior Machine Learning Researcher

APRIL 2019 - PRESENT

Top funded startup Bytedance is revolutionising content creation and consumption through the use of Artificial Intelligence. I am currently part of the London AI Lab where I contribute to state of the Art Machine Learning research.

Jukedeck, London (UK) — *Machine Learning Researcher*

APRIL 2015 - APRIL 2019

At startup Jukedeck we did cutting edge research in the field of music generation with deep learning. The company has been featured in BBC, The Financial Times, The New York Times, Wired and Forbes and won several prizes.

Smartlab University of Trieste, Trieste (IT) — *Internship*

OCTOBER 2011 - APRIL 2012

At SmartLab at the University of Trieste I worked on installing laser and ultrasound sensors on a self driving wheeled robot.

Lionello Stock Middle School, Trieste (IT) — *Clarinet Teacher*

JUNE 2011 - JULY 2011

I was a supply teacher at the Lionello Stock Middle School of Trieste for one month, teaching music theory and clarinet performance.

EDUCATION

La Sapienza University, Rome (IT) — *Master's Degree in Artificial Intelligence and Robotics* October 2012 - APRIL 2015 - GRADE 110/100

I learnt to design and implement artificial intelligence and robotic systems, as well as the interdisciplinary skills that are essential to managing complex projects and their impact on the society.

University of Trieste, Trieste (IT) — *Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering* October 2007 - APRIL 2012

I learnt all the skills required to design software in most programming languages as well as manage complex projects from beginning to end.

Conservatory of Trieste, Trieste (IT) — *Bachelor's Degree in Clarinet Performance* JULY 2010

Here I studied clarinet performance to professional level, and acquired the skills needed to play clarinet in orchestra and chamber music ensembles and teach music theory and clarinet performance.

PUBLICATIONS

StrucutureNet: Inducing Structure in Generated Melodies

The 19th International Society of Music Information Retrieval Conference 2018 http://ismir2018.ircam.fr/doc/pdfs/126_Paper.pdf

SKILLS

Artificial Intelligence

Machine Learning

Deep Learning

Reinforcement Learning

Generative Models

Recurrent Models

Python,

Tensorflow, Theano

Keras

Matlab, octave

Java, c++

HTML, PHP, CSS

LANGUAGES

Italian

Mother Tongue

English

Full Working Proficiency

Proncienc

Spanish

Limited Working Proficiency